<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hello, Brick!</title>
    <link>https://hellobrick.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hello, Brick!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 09:48:56 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hellobrick.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How I started loving LEGO again in my thirties</title>
      <link>https://hellobrick.github.io/blog/how-i-started-loving-lego-again-in-my-thirties/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 08:37:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hellobrick.github.io/blog/how-i-started-loving-lego-again-in-my-thirties/</guid>
      <description>As much as I loved LEGOs during my childhood - I have to admit - I stopped caring about them as soon as I started growing up&amp;hellip; and never thought much about them until very recently.
I suspect this is common to many AFOL.
Six years ago, I became father of the most wonderful little girl&amp;hellip; No, that&amp;rsquo;s not when I re-discovered my passion for LEGOs; at the time, as you might guess, we haven&amp;rsquo;t much free time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our family LEGO portrait</title>
      <link>https://hellobrick.github.io/blog/our-family-lego-portrait/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 17:02:24 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hellobrick.github.io/blog/our-family-lego-portrait/</guid>
      <description>In this period, we - as many of you - are passing almost 100% of our time at home.
One positive aspect of this &amp;ldquo;always staying at home&amp;rdquo;, is that we were able to accomplish lot of things we had postponed for long time, such as our family LEGO portrait.
We bought the minifigs and the picture frame months ago, but never assembled it, till very recently.
We bought the picture frame from IKEA, RIBBA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building Central Perk</title>
      <link>https://hellobrick.github.io/blog/building-central-perk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 10:29:51 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hellobrick.github.io/blog/building-central-perk/</guid>
      <description>This year - as gift for the father&amp;rsquo;s day - I&amp;rsquo;ve received the beautiful Central Perk ~ LEGO 21319 set  .
Being a fan of the TV serie, the gift was twice welcome, and I was looking forward very much to spend a couple of hours on it&amp;hellip; but if I&amp;rsquo;ve been told that the opportunity to build it, would have been given me by the world-level spread of covid-19, I would have gladly declined it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A social-distant weekend</title>
      <link>https://hellobrick.github.io/blog/a-social-distant-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 17:11:40 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hellobrick.github.io/blog/a-social-distant-weekend/</guid>
      <description>Sunday, March 15. Spring is sprung early this year; we can feel the sun is warm outside our windows, and hear chirping of birds. Perfect weather to stay at home, and play LEGO.
Oh, no&amp;hellip; I am not kidding.
Ok, I admit, we like LEGO, and everything, but in similar condition, usually playing with LEGO would be the latest thing we would do. Anyway, this weekend is different, cause there&amp;rsquo;s coronavirus emergence in our country, and our government has recommended to avoid going out if not necessary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://hellobrick.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 09:48:56 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hellobrick.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello there!
… and welcome on Hello, Bricks!, our family LEGO blog.
We like LEGO, and love to play together.
We&amp;rsquo;ve started Hello, Bricks! to share our creations, reviews, experiences and everything else around the wonderful world of LEGO.
Subscribe to our RSS feed to know when new content is published.
Contact: hellobrickblog at gmail dot com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dreambox</title>
      <link>https://hellobrick.github.io/dreambox/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hellobrick.github.io/dreambox/</guid>
      <description>In this page we list the LEGO set we&amp;rsquo;ve bought, or we would like to have in the future. Links are affiliated links; so if you buy, we earn something as well.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>